## Victoria Juszkiewicz

#### Front-end Developer

Front-end Developer with 5 years of social media manager experience combining my technical and social media skills to build tech solutions that have a real positive impact on the user. I am tech savvy, love using tech solutions for many day-to-day problems and would love to contribute to building such products that make people's day-to-day better.

Email +48 690 401 001 LinkedIn GitHub Portfolio

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### CodeOp, Barcelona— Full Stack Developer

January 2023 - March 2023

- 3 months intensive full-time bootcamp covering full stack technologies
- Built 3 full stack projects: an MVP, a Feature Extension and a Group Project

## Goodwinsmith, Redfootshoes, Celebrity Waist Trainers (Remote)-Social Media Manager/Influencer Marketing/ Content Creator

July 2020 - November 2022

- Increased Instagram account engagement by 38% by building and executing a social media strategy through competitive research and platform determination,
- Reached up to 2.2M views on Tik Tok video for my clients by creating viral content,
   building a marketing strategy and building strong relationships with my clients,
- Successfully implemented influencer marketing and affiliate marketing strategies to increase sales,

# Body Safety Ltd (Workwearexperts, Cargo workwear, Chemsplash) Dublin— Digital Marketing Specialist

August 2019 - May 2020

- Managed all social media channels (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Linkedin, Tiktok).
   This required: measuring and reporting on the performance of all digital marketing campaigns, SEO and generation of inbound traffic& identifying Target Customers
- Ensured design consistency between the website, social media channels and email marketing,
- Improved user experience and engagement by collaborating with the development team to define user needs and implement a new form design and website flow-resulting in reduced registration and purchasing time.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

React.js, Vue.js

HTML, CSS

JavaScript

Node.js / Express

MySQL

Postman

GitHub, Git Bash

Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

JSON Web Token,

Bcrypt

Notion, Trello

Figma

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Development Bootcamp - CodeOp January 2023 - March 2023

Professional Diploma in Digital Marketing - IBAT COLLEGE DUBLIN

NFQ Level 5 Certificate-HAIRDRESSER SCHOOL POLAND

#### **LANGUAGES**

Polish (Native)

English (Fluent)

## Spectrum Print Logistic Dublin— Quality Control

May 2015 - April 2016 and February 2017 - August 2019

- Ensured team efficiency by managing task distribution, monitoring and evaluating workers' performance
- Ensured team safety by instructing new employees on safety measures and making sure that work equipment is available

#### **HACKATHON EXPERIENCE**

### Extia— Finalist

July 2023

- My focus during the hackathon was to design an accessible and sustainable widget for the "Welcome Extia" website.
- The Extia Buddy system, which I developed, plays a crucial role in connecting newcomers with local Extia buddies, fostering a supportive and inclusive community within the organization.
- My project answered real problems and was focusing on being accessible for people with different disabilities.
- First version got into finals and second version won.